She's a trip, but she's no vacation.
According to Greta is a drama, romance film directed by Nancy Bardawil.
Dumped on her grandparents for the summer by her indifferent mother, acerbic and
self-destructive teenager Greta disrupts the elderly couple's staid life on the Jersey Shore.
Eventually, a romance helps Greta face down her demons.
Greta, played by Hilary Duff.
Julie, played by Evan Ross.
Katherine, played by Ellen Burstyn.
Joseph, played by Michael Murphy.
Stacy, played by Tsianina Joelson.
Karen, played by Melissa Leo.
According to Greta (released as Surviving Summer in the United Kingdom) is a 2009 American drama film directed by
Nancy Bardawil and starring Hilary Duff, Evan Ross, Melissa Leo, Michael Murphy, and Ellen Burstyn.
The film explores themes of suicide, grandparent grandchild
relationship, suicide attempt, romance, grandparents.
The tone is emotional.